

Contact

Phone

09-977619881

Email

Herryjacker4@gmail.com

Address

Mandalay, Myanmar

Links

Github:

https://github.com/Herry-Jacker

Portfolio

https://herry-jacker.github.io/soe-paing

Skills

| | - | | г. | _ |
|-----|---|----|----|-------|
| ero | | T- | | a T o |

 HTML
 -96%

 CSS
 - 94%

 JavaScript
 - 95%

 React.JS
 - 72%

Back-End

PHP - 52% Laravel - 54%

Design

Photoshop

Figma - 45%

- 40%

Soe Paing

Front-End Developer

About Me

Hello! I am Soe Paing, 23 years old.

I changed my career from hotel life to web developer life.

I have some experience in UI/UX design and frontend development with Team Work.

Now I am studying web development to become my main career and trying to be an Employee of development company.

I love to create responsive and perfect UI designs in a good condition of user experience (UX).

My upcoming plan is to become a fullstackdeveloper.

Work Experiences

Web Designer

Vertical Solution Group / Mar 2022 - Feb 2023

Assistant Manager

Sagaing Golden World Hotel / Jan 2023 – April 2023

FO Supervisor

Sagaing Golden World Hotel / April 2022 – Dec 2022

Education & Knowledge

Geography (second year)

Meikhtila University / Meikhtila , Mandalay , Myanmar

Professional Web Developer

Fairway Technology / Yangon, Myanmar / 2024

Studying In Web Development Knowledges

UI/UX design concept, Front-End, Back-End, API,...